https://www.cactx.org/site-policies

Log In
Username?:
If you have a center location account, use your City name as your username. If you have a Resource Library Membership, then use your e-mail address.
Password:
Forget Your Login?
Forget Your Login?
Enter the e-mail address associated with this account and an e-mail will be sent with password reset information.
Select a county
AndersonAndrewsAngelinaAransasArcherArmstrongAtascosaBanderaBastropBaylorBeeBellBexarBlancoBordenBowieBrazoriaBrazosBrewsterBriscoeBrooksBrownBurlesonBurnetCaldwellCalhounCameronCampCarsonCassCastroChambersCherokeeChildressClayCochranCollinCollingsworthComalCookeCoryellDallamDallasDeaf SmithDeltaDentonDewittDonleyEastlandEctorEl PasoEllisErathFallsFanninFayetteFisherFort BendFranklinFreestoneFrioGalvestonGillespieGonzalesGrayGraysonGreggGrimesGuadalupeHaleHallHansfordHardemanHardinHarrisHarrisonHartleyHaysHemphillHendersonHidalgoHillHockleyHoodHopkinsHoustonHuntHutchisonJasperJeff DavisJeffersonJim WellsJohnsonKarnesKaufmanKendallKenedyKerrKimbleKlebergLamarLambLampasasLasalleLavacaLeeLeonLibertyLimestoneLipscombLive OakLlanoLubbockMadisonMarionMasonMatagordaMcCullochMcLennanMcMullenMedinaMenardMidlandMillsMitchellMontagueMontgomeryMooreMorrisNacogdochesNavarroNewtonNolanNuecesOchiltreeOldhamOrangePalo PintoPanolaParkerParmerPolkPotterPresidioRainsRandallReaganRealRed RiverRobertsRobertsonRockwallRuskSabineSan JacintoSan PatricioSan SabaScurryShelbyShermanSmithSomervellStarrStephensSwisherTarrantTaylorTerrellTerryTitusTom GreenTravisTrinityTylerUpshurUvaldeVan ZandtVictoriaWalkerWardWashingtonWebbWhartonWheelerWichitaWillacyWilliamsonWilsonWoodYoakumYoung
Advanced Search
Site Policies
This website is owned and operated by or on behalf of Children's Advocacy Centers™ of Texas, Inc. We recognize that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
Children's Advocacy Centers™ of Texas, Inc.
1501 W. Anderson Lane, Bldg. B-1
Austin, TX 78757
Or email us at info@cactx.org
We are available to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
Children's Advocacy Centers™ of Texas, Inc. (CACTX) is a non-profit, statewide membership association that serves local independent children’s advocacy center organizations (the "local CACs") around the state of Texas. CACTX represents the largest such membership organization of CACs in the nation.
Each local CAC is a separate legal entity, governed by an independent board of directors, executive committee or other governing body and is solely responsible for its own affairs, including, but not limited to, matters of safety; compliance with federal, state and local laws; physical facilities; uses of technology, finances; policies and programs and personnel policies and decisions. Each local CAC has sole authority to hire, to terminate, to prescribe the duties of and to establish the terms of employment of its employees and officers.
CACTX has no authority with respect to employment policies or decisions of local CACs. Accordingly, each local CAC controls its own affairs and CACTX does not control and cannot be held responsible for the actions of local CACs.
Personal Information
You may visit www.cactx.org without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. However, to access certain portions of the website, you may have to submit information such as a user ID and password, or to access some services we provide, you may have to give us personal information such as your name, address and e-mail.
CACTX collects information in several ways from different parts of this site. CACTX may collect personal information from you when you register with this site. CACTX also may ask you for personal information at other times, such as when you ask a question or report a problem with this site. If you contact CACTX, we may keep a record of that session or correspondence, including a record of your e-mail address. CACTX may also occasionally ask users to complete surveys for research purposes. There also may be services on this site that require you to fill out an online form or send CACTX an e-mail message in order to utilize these services. Any information you provide in such circumstances, including personal information, may be collected.
To access our transaction programs, we may ask you for your address and/or credit card information.
Information security and quality
CACTX intends to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented high grade encryption and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the credit card information you send to us. Companies we work with to process credit card transactions also use high grade encryption and security protocols. You acknowledge, however, that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while CACTX strives to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to or from this site. Contributions may also be made by calling 1-800-255-2574 or directly to your local CAC.
Website traffic information
When you arrive at or leave the CACTX website, we automatically receive the web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our website you visit while you are on our hosted site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our hosted sites. We use this information only to try to better understand visitor preferences and to manage the load on our servers.
Cookies
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive.
Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. If you set your browser to turn off cookies some areas of some sites may not function properly.
We sometimes use cookies to collect non-personal information from visitors to our sites to help us provide better service and facilitate your visit within our site. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous.
CACTX also may collect IP addresses, domain names, and similar items regarding users of this site to measure the number of visits, pages visited, average time spent on this site, and similar items.
Privacy Practices of Other Sites
This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information CACTX collects online through this site, not information that CACTX collects through other sources. For your convenience, this site contains links or addresses to other websites. CACTX is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Carefully review the approach these sites take to your privacy before you use them or provide them with information. CACTX does not share any of the individual personal information you provide us with to the sites to which we link, although we may share aggregate data with such websites (such as how many people use our site).
We assume no liability for any unauthorized actions of third parties or accidental transmission errors that may disclose information about you, and CACTX is not responsible for these other sites' content or privacy policies, which may be different from CACTX' privacy practices.
Disclosure to third parties
CACTX understands the importance of privacy and confidentiality to users of this site. We will only share personally identifiable information with a third party if and when the individual submitting this information has permitted us to do so, or if we are required by law to do so. However, if you become involved in any violation of security or violation of any party's or third party's rights, CACTX may release information about you to assist in investigating or resolving any such incidents.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless the site editor and the site editor's subsidiaries, affiliates, related parties, officers, directors, employees, agents, independent contractors, partners, and co-branders, from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorney's fees, that may be made by any third party, due to or arising out of your conduct or connection with this website or service, your provision of content, your violation of these terms of use, or any other violation of the rights of another person or party.
Children's Online Privacy Protection
While little, if any, of the CACTX website is directed towards children, we are committed to comply with applicable laws and requirements, such as the United States' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We encourage parental supervision for children who are using the internet.
Notification of Changes
CACTX may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. Please consult this Privacy Policy regularly.
View Full Site »
Report Suspected Abuse: 1-800-252-5400
Site by:
TradeMark Media
Site Map
Site Policies
Report A Website Problem
© 2020 Children's Advocacy Centers of Texas, Inc. All rights reserved.
